A Guide to the Papers of W. Ralph Singleton, 1940-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of W. Ralph Singleton 1940-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12766-b
This collection consists of 20500 items (13 linear feet).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Ralph Singleton 1981 Oct. 14.
Scope and Content Information
Papers of W. Ralph Singleton as Miller Professor of Biology and Director of the Blandy Experimental Farm. Also includes papers regarding his work with the Brookhaven National Laboratory and other scientific organizations particularly re his specialty radiation genetics. Biographical data also included and correspondences regarding Accokeek Foundation National Colonial Farm, and his speeches and writings.
Contents List
- Series I. Personal and General Correspondence
  - Personal Correspondence 1945, 1960-1962, 1970-1981, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Accokeek Foundation Annual Reports 1972-1973, 1975 (Box 1)
  - American Genetics Association 1973-1976 (Box 1)
  - Atomic Energy Training Program Desk Memo Book 1963 (Box 1)
  - Biology Department n.d. (Box 1)
  - Biology '61 Class Roll 1970 (Box 1)
  - Bolton, Francis P. 1977 (Box 1)
  - Botany 105 Class Papers-Indian Villages 1956 (Box 1)
  - Bowling, Michael 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Boxwood Society 1973-1978 (Box 1)
  - Brink, R. Alexander-Paramutation n.d. (Box 1)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Bussey Institution, Harvard University 1923, 1971, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Calcutta University 1969-1977 (Box 1)
  - Carpenter, Johnson T., Jr., M.D. 1966 (Box 1)
  - Carter, R. C. 1967 (Box 1)
  - Castle, W. E. 1968-1970 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Dr. T. T., International Rice Research Institute 1969 (Box 1)
  - Chestnuts 1954, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Chestnuts-Miscellaneous Correspondence 1969-1978 (Box 1)
  - Coat Colors 1967 (Box 2)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station 1932, 1956, 1970, 1972-1976 (Box 2)
  - Crookham, George 1969-1978 (Box 2)
  - Dean, George W. 1969 (Box 2)
  - DeKalb Agricultural Association, Inc. 1966 (Box 2)
  - East-West Press-Van Nostrand & Co., W. Dallas Ten Broeck 1966 (Box 2)
  - Eigsti, Dr. O. J. 1966-1968 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Mutagen Society 1970 (Box 2)
  - Expense Accounts-Cuba 1925-1926 (Box 2)
  - Flory, Walter S. 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Galinat, Walton C. 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - Garden Clubs 1975 (Box 2)
  - Garden Mason College 1966 (Box 2)
  - Golden Graduate-Washington State University, Western trip May-June 1972 1972 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Students 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Horses 1970 (Box 2)
  - Horse Correspondence 1961-1967 (Box 2)
  - Horse Genetics 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Hobbs, Horton H., Smithsonian Institution 1969 (Box 2)
  - Husted, Cadley 1966 (Box 2)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency 1965-1970 (Box 2)
  - Keswick Club 1966-1972 (Box 3)
  - Ketterer, Barbara 1968 (Box 3)
  - Lane High School 1966 (Box 3)
  - Ma, Te-Hsiu 1965-1975 (Box 3)
  - Ma, Te Hsiu-Smithsonian Institution 1967-1969 (Box 3)
  - Mackintosh, William 1969 (Box 3)
  - Maize News 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - McClintock, Barbara-Annotated Reprints and Autographed Reprints 1926, 1938, 1950-1951 (Box 3)
  - McCormack, Donald A. 1970 (Box 3)
  - Miller Centennial (1869-1969) 1969 (Box 3)
  - Miller Professor Report 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Muller, H. J. -Radiation Genetics n.d. (Box 3)
  - Mutation Breeding 1963, n.d. (Box 3)
  - National Colonial Foundation 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - National Colonial Farm 1976, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Northeast Regional Plant Introduction Station 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Osborne, T. S.-"Atoms in Agriculture" 1963 (Box 3)
  - Philippine Tour 1963 (Box 3)
  - Reprint Requests 1968 (Box 3)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program 1975 (Box 3)
  - Retirement Dinner 1970 (Box 3)
  - Rice Breeding 1964, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Shannon, Edgar F. 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Straus, Robert W. 1973, 1974, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Stronghold, Inc. 1970-1975, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Taylor, Herbert 1970 (Box 3)
  - University Circle Association 1972-1978 (Box 3)
  - Willrich, Mason 1968 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1926-1979, n.d., 9 folders (Box 4)
- Series II: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Shull, George H. 1914-1951 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Stadler, L. J. 1927-1939 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Mangelsdorf, Paul C. 1928-1951 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Miscellaneous 1934-1947 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Sievers, F. J.; Eisenmenger, Walter S. 1935 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - Vavilov, N. I. 1936 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station - University of Minnesota, Lectures and Seminar (Fall) 1941 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - University of Minnesota (Fall) 1941 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station - Research Data, Radiation Squares for Planting 1945 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence - East, Edward M. 1946 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station Correspondence and Research Notes - Miscellaneous 1947-1949, n.d. (Box 5)
- Series III: Brookhaven National Laboratory
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Mehlquist, G. A. L., Annotated Material 1946-1947 (Box 5)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Data - Hybrid Corn Seed Produced 1947, 1949, 1953-1955 (Box 5)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence and Research Data - Crop Surveys 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Mangelsdorf, A. J. 1949-1950 (Box 5)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Research Notes and Photographs - Gamma Fields 1949-1952 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Progress Reports 1949-1955 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Control Data 1950 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Stadler, L. J. 1950, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Economic Cooperative Administration (Indonesia) 1951 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Education 1952 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Matthews, D. L. 1952 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1952, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Research Statistics and Photographs 1952 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence and Research Data - Control Summary 1952-1953 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence and Printed Matter - International Genetics Congress 1952-1953 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Public Health Fellows 1952-1954 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1952-1955 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - International Genetics Congress 1953 (Box 6)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Oliver, Dr. Clarence P. 1953 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Carnation Correspondence Research Data 1953-1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Ritchie, Allen 1953-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Animal Breeding 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Atomic Energy Commission, Genetic Applications using Radiation in Plant and Animal Improvements 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Florida Corn 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - List of Persons Receiving copy of Hearings on Atomic Energy and Agriculture 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Maize Genetics Cooperation 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Mavor, James W.; Whitney Willis R. 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Whitney, Willis R. 1954 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence and Research Data - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC) 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Berkner, Lloyd V. 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Blandy Experimental Farm 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Reynolds, Bruce 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Sigma XI 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Charlottesville, Virginia 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Darden, Colgate W., Jr. 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - International Conference on Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, Geneva. Switzerland 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Research Data, Memos: Pollination Instructions 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, Mertens, Thomas R. 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Meteorological Measurements during 1955 Corn Mutation Experiments at BNL 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Pearson, Paul (AEC) 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory - Short Corn Hybrids 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - University of Virginia 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - U. Va. Press Release 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - White, O. E., Blandy Experimental Farm 1955 (Box 7)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory Correspondence - Reynolds, Bruce 1955-1957 (Box 7)
- Series IV: Blandy Experimental Farm
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - East, E. M. 1911 (Box 7)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Goldschmidt 1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Miller Professor of Biology, Annual Reports 1956-1960 1951, 1956-1960 (Box 7)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1953 (Box 7)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Reports, Minutes - Blandy Farm Committee 1953-1954 (Box 7)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - National Science Foundation 1953-1958 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1954 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Good, Edward 1954, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Radiation Applications Inc. 1954-1958 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farms - Fulbright Awards 1954-1959 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Castle, W. E. 1954, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Board of Visitors 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Brookhaven National Laboratory 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Colonnade Club 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Corn 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Curriculum Committee 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Darden, Colgate W., Jr. 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "J" File 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - National Research Center 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Purchases 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Quarles, Lawrence (Dean) 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Singleton, Ralph 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - 1955 Data Sheets 1955 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - American Seed Trade Association 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "B" File 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Beckerley, James 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Brookhaven National Laboratory 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "C" Files 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence and Data - Casper, Alan 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "D" File 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "E" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "F" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Memos - Faculty 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Walter Flory 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Fulbright 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "G" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "H" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Hammond, Lewis M., Dean of Graduate School 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "I" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "K" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "L" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "M" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "N" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Oak Ridge National Laboratory 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "P" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "R" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Radiation Applications Inc. 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "S" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Students 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "T" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "W" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "Z" File 1955-1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Fellows (Prospective) 1955-1957 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Husted, Ladley 1955-1957 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Rappaport, Jacques J. 1955-1960 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Flory, Walter S. 1955-1962 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Caldwell, W. H., Commissioner, Division of Planning & Economic Development 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Curtis, Howard L. 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence, Memos - Duren, Dean 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Fellowship Renewals 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - For Attention Later" 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Genetics Class 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Graduate School Announcements 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Hybrid Corn 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Mountain Lake 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - National Academy of Science 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "O" File 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Old Dominion Foundation, Appendix A and B 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence and Data - Plant Introductions 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence and Data - Roses 1956 (Box 9)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Shea, Vincent 1956 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Southern Regional Education Board 1956 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Stanley, Thomas B., Governor 1956 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - V. P. I. 1956 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - National Academy of Science, Maynard, L. A. 1956-1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - White, O. E., Arboretum 1956-1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Darden, Colgate W., Jr. 1956-1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Biology Department Letters 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Biology Positions, University of Virginia 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Curriculum Committee 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Lane High School 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Vaughan, Joe 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Yarnell, Dr. S. H. Yarnell 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Old Dominion Foundation Proposal Research Grant 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Minutes - Reynolds Memoranda 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1957 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Atomic Energy Commission 1957-1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Reports - Atomic Energy Commission, Geneva Conference, Sept. 1958 1957-1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Memoranda - Dent, J. N. 1957-1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Hammond, Lewis M. 1957-1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Current Project 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Genetics Society of America 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Maize News Letter 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Phi Sigma (Beta Beta Beta) 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Hunter, Wilbur 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Letters to the Editor 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1958 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - International Cooperation Administration International Program 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Fellowships Available 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - National Academy of Sciences Plant Breeding Committee 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Osborne, T. S. 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - McCormick, Dewey 1958, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Arboretum, White, Orland E. 1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm- Chestnuts and Literature Farm File 1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Library 1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Virginia - State Government Virginia Advisory Legislative Council 1959 (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Wallace, Henry A. 1959, (TMs or copy of speech w/corrections of Henry Wallace, Washington, D. C. January 8, '59) (Box 10)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data -1959 Data Sheets 1959 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence and Date - Casper, Alan 1959-1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Lerner, I. Michael 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Runk, B. F. D. 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Shaw, Richard F. 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - 1960 Radiation Experiments 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data & Photographs - 1960 Summary Data 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - Summary 1960 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Casper, Alan 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - "F" File 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Gowen, Dr. John W. 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Medical College of Virginia 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Science Service, Things of Science 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Wittmeyer, E. C. 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Statistics - 1961 Experimental Stage 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Statistics - C.B.C., corn for 1961 1961 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - 1961-1962, Experiment #1 1961-1962 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Atomic Energy Commission License 1962 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Hobbs, H. H. 1962 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Flory, Walter S. 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - 1963 Data 1963 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence Research Notes - Atomic Energy Commission Ms Material 1963-1965 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Goswami, U. L. 1964 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence and Minutes - Arboretum 1964 1964 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Notes and Lists - Atomic Energy Commission, Dr. Chatterjee 1964 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - 1964 Experiment #1 Summary 1964 (Box 11)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Reports - Shannon, Edgar, Report (Revised) 1964 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm 1965 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Expenses 1965 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - International Atomic Energy Agency Telephone Directory 1965 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Notes, Printed Matter - Proembryos in maize 1965 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Miller Board 1965-1967 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence, Reports - Atomic Energy Commission 1965-1967 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Corn Inbreds 1966 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Godwin, Mills E., Jr. 1966 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence, Reports - AEC Contract 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Atomic Energy Terminal Report 1967 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence, Printed Matter - Atomic Energy Commission Summary, Programs 1967 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Atomic Energy Commission 1969 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Correspondence - Old Dominion Foundation 1971, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Building Plans n.d. (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm - Giles, Norman Henry n.d. (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Memos - Redfield, Admiral n.d. (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Data - Control Data n.d. (Box 12)
  - Bland Experimental Farm Research Notes, Reports n.d. (Box 12)
- Series V: Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1963 Dec-1965 Mar (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Clippings 1964 (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - International Atomic Energy Agency - Goswami, U. L. 1964 (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Reports 1964 (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Prajayantra Company Limited 1964 (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Rice Department, Ministry of Agriculture 1964 (Box 12)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Rockefeller Foundation 1964 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Address Book, Business Card 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - MacDonald, Macolm M. 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Reactor, Dr. Suasti Srisukh 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Singleton, Dorothy, News Story 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Talks in Bangkok 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Thailand, Scientific Development 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - United Nations Tab 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Virginia National Bank 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - MacDonald, Macolm M. 1964-1966 (Box 13)
  - Atomic Energy Laboratory (Kasetsart University) - Colleagues in Asia 1965 (Box 13)